Quick Jump

Quick Jump

Menu

Install the app

Install

*  Light/Dark

* [](https://sanctioned-suicide.net/account/dismiss-notice?notice_id=51 "Dismiss notice")Hey Guest,
    
    If you would still like to donate, you still can. We have more than enough funds to cover operating expenses for quite a while, so don't worry about donating if you aren't able. If you want to donate something other than what is listed, you can contact RainAndSadness.
    
    Bitcoin Address (BTC): 39deg9i6Zp1GdrwyKkqZU6rAbsEspvLBJt
    
    Ethereum (ETH): 0xd799aF8E2e5cEd14cdb344e6D6A9f18011B79BE9
    
    Monero (XMR): 49tuJbzxwVPUhhDjzz6H222Kh8baKe6rDEsXgE617DVSDD8UKNaXvKNU8dEVRTAFH9Av8gKkn4jDzVGF25snJgNfUfKKNC8

Privacy policy
==============

JavaScript is disabled. For a better experience, please enable JavaScript in your browser before proceeding.

You are using an out of date browser. It may not display this or other websites correctly.  
You should upgrade or use an [alternative browser](https://www.google.com/chrome/).

Help pages

Help
----

* Privacy policy 

We are Sanctioned Suicide ("we", "our", "us"). We’re committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. If you have questions about your personal information please [contact us](https://sanctioned-suicide.net/misc/contact).

What information we hold about you
----------------------------------

The type of data that we collect and process includes:

* Your name or username.
* Your email address.
* Your IP address.

Further data may be collected if you choose to share it, such as if you fill out fields on your profile.

We collect some or all of this information in the following cases:

* You register as a member on this site.
* You fill out our contact form.
* You browse this site. See "Cookie policy" below.
* You fill out fields on your profile.

How your personal information is used
-------------------------------------

We may use your personal information in the following ways:

* For the purposes of making you a registered member of our site, in order for you to contribute content to this site.
* We may rarely use your email address to inform you of activity on our site.
* Your IP address is recorded when you perform certain actions on our site. Your IP address is never publicly visible.

Other ways we may use your personal information.
------------------------------------------------

In addition to notifying you of activity on our site which may be relevant to you, from time to time we may wish to communicate with all members any important information such as newsletters or announcements by email. You can opt-in to or opt-out of such emails in your profile.

We may collect non-personally identifiable information about you in the course of your interaction with our site. This information may include technical information about the browser or type of device you're using. This information will be used purely for the purposes of analytics and tracking the number of visitors to our site.

Keeping your data secure
------------------------

We are committed to ensuring that any information you provide to us is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable measures and procedures to safeguard and secure the information that we collect.

Cookie policy
-------------

Cookies are small text files which are set by us on your computer which allow us to provide certain functionality on our site, such as being able to log in, or remembering certain preferences.

We have a detailed cookie policy and more information about the cookies that we set on [this page](https://sanctioned-suicide.net/help/cookies).

Rights
------

You have a right to modify your personal information at any time from your preferences panel, and to ask any questions by using the [contact form](https://sanctioned-suicide.net/misc/contact).

Further Rules
-------------

This site has further specific rules which can be read by clicking the link in the navigation bar. If you can't find the link please contact a moderator.

Acceptance of this policy
-------------------------

Any continued use of our site signifies your acceptance of this policy. If you do not accept the policy then please do not use this site.

Changes to this policy
----------------------

We may make changes to this policy at any time. You may be asked to review and re-accept the information in this policy if it changes in the future.

CAPTCHA privacy policy
----------------------

This site is protected by hCaptcha and its [privacy policy](https://hcaptcha.com/privacy) and [terms of service](https://hcaptcha.com/terms) apply.

Community platform by XenForo® © 2010-2024 XenForo Ltd.

* This site uses cookies to help personalise content, tailor your experience and to keep you logged in if you register.  
    By continuing to use this site, you are consenting to our use of cookies.
